Guide to the Robert B. Fisher Photograph Collection and Papers WA MSS S-2823
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Stereographs, 1850-1975; Series II; 4.2; 5 boxes
  - Card Stereographs
    - Graver, Nicholas M.
      Nicholas M. Graver (born 1937) worked as a medical photographer at University of Rochester School of Medicine and Dentistry, as well as the Kodak Research Laboratories
      - Portrait of William Culp Darrah, Gettysburg, Pennsylvania (No. 50), A Second Century of Stereoscopic Views, 1975 August 22 (Box 11, Folder 357)
    - Griffith Griffith
      In 1896, George William Griffith (1864-1909) and his brother created Griffith & Griffith in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
      - Chateau Road to the Cascade, Nice, France (No. 7286), unidentified series, circa 1900 (Box 11, Folder 358)
    - H. C. White Co.
      - Palace of Electricity at night, looking from Lower West Cascade (No. 8509), Louisiana Purchase Exposition, 1904 (Box 11, Folder 359)
    - Jackson, William Henry
      William Henry Jackson (1843-1942) was an American photographer and publisher known for his images of the American West
      - Devil's Slide, Weber Canyon (No. 101), Scenery of the Union Pacific Railroad, circa 1870 (Box 11, Folder 360)
    - John Anderson Publishing Co.
      - View of a church, probably in Norway (no number), unidentified series, circa 1900 (Box 11, Folder 361)
    - Keystone View Company
      Benneville Lloyd Singley (1864-1938) founded the Keystone View Company in 1892, and it became a major distributor of stereographic images until 1963.
      - Rock of Gibraltar (No. 966), unidentified series, 1895 (Box 11, Folder 362)
      - The President and Mrs. McKinley (No. 2474), unidentified series, 1897 (Box 11, Folder 363)
      - Old Weir Bridge, Lakes of Killarney, Ireland (No. 2529), unidentified series, 1897 (Box 11, Folder 364)
      - Me an' Billy (No. 9685), unidentified series, 1899 (Box 11, Folder 365)
      - Reflection (No. 10475), unidentified series, 1901 (Box 11, Folder 366)
      - The Little Protector (No. 11426), unidentified series, 1907 (Box 11, Folder 367)
      - Harvesting in the Great West - Combined Reaper and Thresher - Washington U.S.A. (No. 11623), unidentified series, 1901 (Box 11, Folder 368)
      - Overlooking the Thames at 11 o'clock at Night. London, England (No. 13101), unidentified series, 1903 (Box 11, Folder 369)
      - One of the Great Trees that Grow in the Rainy Northwest Showing Method of Felling, Oregon (No. 13567), unidentified series, 1903 (Box 11, Folder 370-371)
        2 copies of the same image
      - Great Trees in the Oregon Forest (No. 13569), unidentified series, 1903 (Box 11, Folder 372)
      - Hydraulic Mining, Ore. (No. 13796), unidentified series, circa 1903 (Box 11, Folder 373)
      - An Active Volcano in Java (No. 16400), unidentified series, 1919 (Box 11, Folder 374)
      - A Startling Privilege of the Age - Seeing the World Metropolis from an Airplane, New York City (No. 26293), unidentified series, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 375)
      - Picturesque Grandeur of Columbia River, West Past "Pillars of Hercules," Oregon (No. V26515), unidentified series, circa 1910 (Box 11, Folder 376)
        Original photograph by Underwood & Underwood
      - Great Trees that Grow in the Northwest, Showing Method of Felling, Oregon (No. 29234), unidentified series, circa 1926 (Box 11, Folder 377)
      - A Spectacular Conflagration Raging in a Great Oil Field (No. 32718), unidentified series, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 378)
    - Keystone View Company of New England
      - Mae Duffie School, Springfield, Massachusetts (no number), unidentified series, circa 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 379)
    - Kilburn, Benjamin West
      Benjamin West Kilburn (1827-1909) was an American photographer and stereoscopic view publisher.
      - Profile Lake, Franconia Notch (No. 110), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 11, Folder 380)
      - New York, from the pier of the Suspension Bridge (No. 3095), unidentified series, circa 1885 (Box 11, Folder 381)
      - The Fountain of Administration, World's Fair, Chicago (No. 8618), unidentified series, 1894 (Box 11, Folder 382)
      - Consider the lilies how they grow: they toil not, they spin not; and yet I say unto you that Solomon in all his glory was not arrayed like one of these (No. 10273), unidentified series, 1895 (Box 11, Folder 383)
      - Old Glory (No. 12308), unidentified series, 1898 (Box 11, Folder 384)
      - The Portico of Ramses II, of Great Peristyle Court of Luxor Temple, Egypt (No. 12575), unidentified series, 1898 (Box 11, Folder 385)
        Photograph by James M. Davis
      - Niagara Falls (no number), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 11, Folder 386)
    - J. J. Killelea Co.
      Photographs originally created by the H. C. White Co.
      - Trafalgar Square and Nelson Monument, London, England (No. 2518), unidentified series, circa 1910 (Box 11, Folder 387)
      - The Imposing Matterhorn (No. 5262 ?), unidentified series, circa 1910 (Box 11, Folder 388)
    - Lewis, Russell B.
      Russell B. Lewis (1835-1924) was a photographer in Hudson and Feltonville, Massachusetts
      - Morning Glories (no number), unidentified series, 1874 (Box 11, Folder 389)
    - London Stereoscopic Co.
      - The Fair Deceiver (no number), unidentified series, circa 1880 (Box 11, Folder 390)
    - Moore, J. Robert
      J. Robert Moore (1841-1909) was a photographer in Trenton Falls, new York, circa 1872-1890, as well as a hotel operator in Chelan, Washington, circa 1890-1909.
      - Suydam Fall, Trenton Falls, New York (no number), unidentified series, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 391)
    - Notman, William
      - Cacouna Bay, Quebec (No. 33447), unidentified series, circa 1880 (Box 11, Folder 392)
        Blind stamp: C.R. Chisholm & Bros., Montreal
    - Photographie J. D.
      - Parc des Buttes Chaumont (no number), Nouveau Paris Et Ses Environs, circa 1880 (Box 11, Folder 393)
    - S. B.
      - At Shaldon, near Leymouth, Devon, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 394)
      - Babbacombe, Devon, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 395)
      - Dazon Rock, near Torquay (no number), unidentified series, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 396)
      - Ffos Noddyn, or Glen of the Faries, North Wales, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 397)
      - Lynmouth, North Devon, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 398)
      - Mill near Betws-y-Coed, North Wales, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 399)
      - Near the "Waters Meet," Lynmouth, North Devon, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 400)
      - Sandsfoot Castle (no number), unidentified series, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 401-402)
        Two discrete photographs
      - The Slopes, Sherborne, Dorset, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 403)
      - Tintern Abbey, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 404)
      - Waterloo Bridge, near Llanrwst, North Wales, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 405)
    - Seaver, Chandler, Jr.
      Chandler Seaver, Jr. (1839-1879) was a photographer in Boston, Massachusetts
      - Vicinity of Boston (No. 1187), Park and Garden Series, 1872 (Box 11, Folder 406)
        Published by Charles Pollock, Boston, Massachusetts
    - Sommer, Georgio
      Giorgio Sommer (1834–1914) was a German photographer active in Switzerland, 1856-1866, and Naples, Italy, 1866-1888
      - Cattedrale (Palermo) (No. 506), Napoli, circa 1885 (Box 11, Folder 407)
      - Marina, Palermo (No. 520), Napoli, circa 1885 (Box 11, Folder 408)
      - Panorama da Porta nuova (Palermo) (No. 502), Napoli, circa 1885 (Box 11, Folder 409)
      - Porta felice Palermo (No. 515), Napoli, circa 1885 (Box 11, Folder 410)
    - Soule, John P.
      John P. Soule (1828-1904) was a photographer and publisher in Boston, Massachusetts, and Seattle, Washington.
      - Bastion Fall, Kaaterskill Gorge, Catskill Mt. (No. 426), American Views, circa 1865 (Box 11, Folder 411)
      - Faneuil Hall, Boston (no number), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 11, Folder 412)
        Copy photograph of an original photograph by Soule
      - Niagara - The Horse-Shoe Fall (Moonlight) (No. 1014), American Views, circa 1865 (Box 11, Folder 413)
      - Niagara River, from below Suspension Bridge (No. 331), American Scenery - Niagara Falls and Vicinity, circa 1865 (Box 11, Folder 414)
    - Sunbeam Tours
      - London
        - Charing Cross (No. 1), London, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 415)
        - Trafalgar Square (No. 2), London, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 416)
        - Whitehall (No. 3), London, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 417)
        - House of Parliament (No. 7), London, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 418)
        - Westminster Abbey (No. 11), London, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 419)
        - Piccadilly Circus (No. 14), London, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 420)
        - Hyde Park Corner (No.15), London, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 421)
        - Buckingham Palace (No. 18), London, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 422)
        - Tower Bridge (No. 29), London, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 423)
        - Byward Gate (No. 31), London, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 424)
        - Traitor's Gate (No. 32), London, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 425)
        - Cheapside (No. 34), London, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 426)
        - Royal Exchange (No. 36), London, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 427)
      - London Zoo
        - Hippo, Yawning (No. 22), London Zoo, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 428)
        - Tortoise (No. 24), London Zoo, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 429)
        - Pelicans (No. 31), London Zoo, circa 1924 (Box 11, Folder 430)
    - Tairraz, Joseph
      Joseph Tairraz (1827-1902) was a photographer and alpine guide in Chamonix, France
      - Le Mauvais Pas (No. 25), Vues De Chamonix, 1872 (Box 11, Folder 431)
    - Underwood Underwood
      Underwood & Underwood was founded by Bert Elias Underwood (1862-1943) and his brother Elmer Underwood (1860-1947) in Ottawa, Kansas, 1882. The firm built an international business by popularizing the stereograph.
      - Samuel J. Dixon crossing Niagara on a rope below the great cantilever bridge, U.S.A. (No. 5409), unidentified series, 1890 (Box 11, Folder 432)
      - The Artist's Dream, Hunnewell's Grounds, Wellesley, Mass., U.S. (no number), unidentified series, 1894 (Box 11, Folder 433)
        Photograph by J. F. Jarvis
      - The Children's Pets (no number), unidentified series, 1894 (Box 11, Folder 434)
        Photograph by William H. Rau
      - Empty folder (Box 11, Folder 435)
      - McKinley and Wife (No. 1932), unidentified series, 1896 (Box 11, Folder 436)
        Photograph by Littleton View Co.
      - Along the Appian Way, constructed 4th century, B.C., from Rome to Brindisi, Italy (no number), unidentified series, 1897 (Box 11, Folder 437)
      - Suffer little Children to come unto me (no number), unidentified series, 1897 (Box 11, Folder 438)
        Photograph by Strohmayer and Wyman
      - The Tiber, Castle of St. Angelo and St. Peter's Church, Rome, Italy (no number), unidentified series, 1897 (Box 11, Folder 439)
      - An Artist in his line (no number), unidentified series, 1898 (Box 11, Folder 440)
      - Gotenberg's great market - largest in Sweden (no number), unidentified series, 1900 (Box 11, Folder 441)
      - Sunset, Lake Geneva, Switzerland (No. 1811), unidentified series, 1901 (Box 11, Folder 442)
      - A Terrible Volcanic Explosion - Mont Pelee in eruption, June 5, 1902, Martinique (no number), unidentified series, 1902 June 5 (Box 11, Folder 443)
      - A Terrible Volcanic Explosion - Mont Pelée in eruption, June 1902, Martinique (no number), unidentified series, 1902 June (Box 11, Folder 444)
      - Moonlight on the Cedar Rapids of the St. Lawrence River (no number), unidentified series, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 445)
      - Seining for Salmon in the Columbia River - hauling in the Seine - Oregon (no number), unidentified series, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 446)
      - Consider the lilies how they grow - Solomon in all his glory was not arrayed like one of these (No. 7360), unidentified series, 1903 (Box 11, Folder 447)
      - Sunset on an Orient Sea - off Ceylon, the "Pearl on the brow of Ind" (No. 8719), unidentified series, 1903 (Box 11, Folder 448)
      - Surveying the Grand Cañon of Arizona - at work on Sentinel Point (no number), unidentified series, 1903 (Box 11, Folder 449)
      - A Wonder to the primitive inhabitants - Santa Fe Train crossing Cañon Diablo, Arizona (no number), unidentified series, 1903 (Box 11, Folder 450)
      - Four queens and a jack (no number), unidentified series, 1904 (Box 11, Folder 451)
      - Girls picking tea on famous plantation at Uji, among the sunny hills of old Japan (No. 3915), unidentified series, 1904 (Box 11, Folder 452)
      - Irrigating a strawberry field; Hood river valley, N. to Mt. Adams, Oregon (No. 9864), unidentified series, circa 1910 (Box 11, Folder 453)
    - Union View Co.
      - Two Men and Two Sleeping Women (no number), English Group Series, circa 1880 (Box 11, Folder 454)
    - Vallée, Louis-Prudent
      Louis-Prudent Vallée (1837-1905) was a Canadian photographer working in Quebec
      - Break neck steps at the foot of which was found the tomb of Champlain (No. 63), Canadian Scenery, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 455)
      - Icy Bridge Showing the Island of Orleans, Quebec (no number), Canadian Scenery, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 456)
    - Viking View Company
      - Sioux Falls, South Dakota (no number), unidentified series, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 457)
        Photograph by E. J. Anderson
    - Walker, Lewis E.
      Lewis E. Walker (1826-1916) was a photographer, stereograph publisher, and bookseller in Warsaw, New York
      - Lower Falls of Genesee and Gorge, at Portage, N.Y. (No. 794), Views on the Line of Erie Railway, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 458)
    - Walton, William C.
      William C. Walton (born 1931) is a retired army enlisted man and stereographic photographer and collector in Columbus, Georgia
      - Back to Basics (No.176), unidentified series, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 459)
    - Woodward, Charles Warren.
      - Trout - A Day's Sport (No. 1717), Pennsylvania Scenery, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 460)
        Charles Warren Woodward (1836-1894) was a photographer in Rochester, New York
    - Unidentified
      - After a Storm Comes a Calm (No. 160), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 461)
      - Athens - Theatre of Baachus. State Chairs (No. 55), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 462)
      - Bois de Boulogne (no number), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 463)
      - La Bourse (no number), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 464)
      - Causeway before Washington Hotel during the arrival of the Duke of Windsor, possibly in Boston, Massachusetts (no number), unidentified series, 1860 (Box 12, Folder 465)
      - Devil's Slide, Hell Gate Cañon, Belt Mountains, Montana, 1500 feet high (no number), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 466)
      - Devil's Slide, Weber Canyon, Utah (no number), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 467)
      - Dresde, Saxe, Le Zurieger Côté Sud (No. 4937), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 468)
      - Dumbarton Castle - Ireland (No. 342), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 469)
      - Exterior group playing croquet and sitting near a fountain (no number), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 470)
      - Friends in Adversity (No. 155), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 471)
      - General View of Niagara from Point View (No. 44), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 472)
      - Lake Geneva (no number), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 473)
      - Mother dog and her puppies in a garage (no number), unidentified series, circa 1915 (Box 12, Folder 474)
      - Niagara, Part of Table Rock and Horse Shoe Falls (No. 15), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 475)
      - Omnibuses at South Ferry, New York City (No. 364), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 476)
      - On Smith's Island (no number), Views in and about Philadelphia, 1859 (Box 12, Folder 477)
      - Pont Aberglaslyn, North Wales (No. 565), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 478)
      - Saint Anthony Falls, Minneapolis, Minnesota (no number), unidentified series, circa 1875 (Box 12, Folder 479)
      - Shipyard, including a ship of the Hudson River Transportation Co., possibly New York City, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 480)
      - Steamboat (no number), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 481)
      - "Wooding Up" On the Mississippi (no number), unidentified series, circa 1880 (Box 12, Folder 482)
        Copy photograph of a lithograph engraved by Frances F. Palmer (1812-1876) and published by Currier & Ives in 1863
      - Wray Castle, Windermere (no number), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 483)
      - You have put your foot in it, street scene in England in the days of big hoops (no number), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 12, Folder 484)
    - Non-photographic stereographs
      - Dennis, John Charles
        John Charles Dennis was an optician at 122 Bishopsgate Street, London, from 1850-1862
        - Advertising Polyorama Panoptique et Diagraphique and other optical amusements, circa 1850 (Box 12, Folder 485)
      - Holmes, Frederick H.
        - Holmes's Stereoscopic Diagrams, 1852 (Box 12, Folder 486-488)
      - Unidentified creator
        - Stereographs with printed drawings, circa 1850-1860 (Box 12, Folder 489-502)
- Glass Transparencies and Lantern Slides, circa 1850-circa 1921; Series III; 9.1; 11 boxes
  Series III is organized into six subseries: Glass Transparencies, Magic Lantern Slides with Movement, Magic Lantern Slides, Panorama Lantern Slides, Lantern Slides by Identified Photographers, and Lantern Slides by Unidentified Photographers.
  Headings in each subseries are arranged alphabetically by identified creators followed by items with unidentified creators. Items under each name are arranged either chronologically, alphabetically by title, or sequentially by lantern slide number.
  This series consists of glass transparencies and lantern slides, which are formats designed for viewing by transmitted light. The material chiefly consists of transparent positive photographs, as well as some transparent non-photographic images that are designed for projection viewing or as intermediates for reproduction.
  Individual titles and dates of lantern slides were not captured during processing the collection.
  - Glass Transparencies
    - Fenton, Roger, attributed
      Roger Fenton (1819-1869) was appointed the first official photographer of the British Museum in 1853
      - Copy photograph of the Magna Carta at the British Museum, circa 1854-1858 (Box 13, Folder 502a)
    - Unidentified photographers
      - Microphotographic transparencies, circa 1890-1900; (10 glass slides) (Box 13, Folder 502b)
        Glass transparencies, 1 cm. by 8.6 cm., that have ten images, 0.6 cm. by 0.6 cm.
      - Sculpture, End of the Trail, by James Earle Fraser at the Panama-Pacific International Exposition, 1915; (1 autochrome presented as a lantern slide) (Box 13, Folder 502c)
  - Magic Lantern Slides with Movement
    - E. P.
      - Drachensteigen, a magic lantern slide with a single rack work movement, No. 63, circa 1850 (Box 14, Folder 503)
        Depicts an animated drawing of two children playing with a kite
    - Unidentified creators
      - Chromatrope magic lantern slide with double rack work movement, no number, circa 1850 (Box 14, Folder 504)
      - Bird and cage, a magic lantern slide with a single slipper slide movement, No. 337, circa 1850 (Box 14, Folder 505)
      - Magician and demon, a magic lantern slide with a single slipper slide movement, No. 460, circa 1850 (Box 14, Folder 506)
      - Man and a monkey, a magic lantern slide with a single slipper slide movement, no number, circa 1850 (Box 14, Folder 507)
      - Silence, a magic lantern slide with a single slipper slide movement, no number, circa 1850 (Box 14, Folder 508)
  - Magic Lantern Slides
    - T. H. McAllister
      - Mother's Grave. Children with flowers, no number, circa 1880 (Box 14, Folder 509)
        Drawing depicts three girls and a dog at a gravesite
        Blindstamps on the wooden frame for T. H. McAllister, New York, and Sam C. Partridge, San Francisco
      - Ninety and Nine. "And altho' the road be rough and steep," no number, circa 1880 (Box 14, Folder 510)
        Photograph of a rocky landscape
        Blindstamp on the wooden frame for T. H. McAllister, New York
    - Unidentified creators
      - Ruins of armory at Harper's Ferry, no number, circa 1865 (Box 14, Folder 511)
        Mounted left side of a glass stereograph
      - Niagara Falls at winter with ice, no number, circa 1865-1870 (Box 14, Folder 512)
  - Panorama Lantern Slides
    Panorama lantern slides are rectangular glass lantern slides that usually comprise three to five circular or square photographic images.
    - Montgomery Ward Co.
      - Panorama lantern slide with three images that depict men and women with infants, as well as men assisting a woman onto a streetcar, circa 1875 (Box 14, Folder 513)
    - Numbered slides with an unidentified creator
      Panorama lantern slides with collodion emulsion with five images on a location or subject. Each slide has a number, as well as sequential numbers assigned to each image
      - Mississippi, Slide No. 7, Image No. 31-35, circa 1870 (Box 14, Folder 514)
      - African Americans, Slide No. 8, Image No. 36-40, circa 1870; (2 lantern slides) (Box 14, Folder 515-516)
      - New England, Slide No. 10, Image No. 46-50, circa 1870 (Box 14, Folder 517)
      - Niagara Falls and vicinity, Slide No. 12, Image No. 50-56, circa 1870 (Box 14, Folder 518)
      - White Mountains, New Hampshire, Slide No. 13, Image No. 61-65, circa 1870 (Box 14, Folder 519)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Slide No. 14, Image No. 66-70, circa 1870 (Box 14, Folder 520)
      - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Slide No. 16, Image No. 76-80, circa 1870 (Box 14, Folder 521)
    - Unidentified creator
      - Panorama lantern slide with three images including a drawing of a girl and a dog under the word "Welcome," as well as two drawings of anthropomorphic ants, circa 1885 (Box 14, Folder 522)
      - Panorama lantern slide with five images including the Washington Monument; a man and boy planning to slaughter a turkey and duck, a boy and girl; and anthropomorphic birds singing; as well as a drawing of a girl and a dog under the words "Good Night", circa 1885 (Box 14, Folder 523)
    - Unidentified creators
      - Panorama lantern slide with four pictorial images that depict a black man singing to a white woman; two images of a child and dog tugging after the same doll; and an ocean scene with waders, circa 1870 (Box 14, Folder 524)
      - Panorama lantern slide with four pictorial images that depict biblical scenes, including the annunciation of the angel Gabriel to Mary; Mary and Joseph en route to Bethlehem; a manger scene with an infant Jesus; and the three magi, circa 1870 (Box 14, Folder 525)
      - Panorama lantern slide with five humorous drawings that depict a man before and after war, as well as a sequence showing a cannon mounted to the back of a donkey, circa 1870 (Box 14, Folder 526)
      - Panorama lantern slide with four humorous drawings that depict anthropomorphic toads and birds, as well as a photograph of a laughing man's face, circa 1870 (Box 14, Folder 527)
      - Panorama lantern slide with five photographs of sculpture that represent women and children, circa 1870 (Box 14, Folder 528)
      - Panorama lantern slide with four humorous drawings that depict children playing and a man kissing a woman, as well as a pair of images that show two black men with a donkey, circa 1870 (Box 14, Folder 529)
  - Lantern Slides by Identified Photographers